Everyone knows that Claude skills
make Claude literally 100x more powerful,
but nobody's telling you the exact skills
that you need to install.
So here are my top Claude skills
that I'm using every single day.
And if you comment SKILLS 👉
I'll send all of these across to you.
Now first up is one of my favourites
and it's called Marketing Skills.
This will install 7 marketing agents that do
everything from SEO
Creative writing,
coming up with creative ideas,
email marketing and so much more.
Next up we have awesome skills.
This makes Claude perform actions
like replying to your emails,
posting to Slack,
building entire apps and so much more.
Next up is Banana Claude.
This allows you to use nano banana
inside of your Claude
so it can generate all of your images.
Next up is remotion.
This allows you to create AI
motion graphics or entire videos
from a single prompt.
Next is content engineering
and this reduces the number of tokens
that Claude's using
so you can simply just use way more Claude.